<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Mapping Black Philly Art</title>
    <link>//templedss.github.io/LEADING/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Mapping Black Philly Art</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 23 Aug 2022 10:19:26 -0400</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="//templedss.github.io/LEADING/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Pelle Notes</title>
      <link>//templedss.github.io/LEADING/post/pelle-notes/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Aug 2022 10:19:26 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//templedss.github.io/LEADING/post/pelle-notes/</guid>
      <description>Pelle&amp;rsquo;s Notes: Using Hugo to build a simple static site. Hugo is a useful tool for creating a website. In these notes, I will refer to using Hugo alongside Github. Github is used here both as a place to store the code for your site so that you can collaborate with others and access it from any computer, and as a way of hosting your site (putting it online so others can see it).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Resources</title>
      <link>//templedss.github.io/LEADING/resources/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Jul 2022 14:30:34 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//templedss.github.io/LEADING/resources/</guid>
      <description>Black Philly Artists in Wikidata Sample work of art For querying Wikidata, see our Wikidata repository: https://github.com/TempleDSS/Wikidata
For background on this project, see the four blog posts on the Scholars Studio blog:
Designing a Wikidata Project: Mapping Black Philly Art Curious about Wikidata but not sure where to start? In this beginner-friendly blog post, Dr. Synatra Smith explains how to get started with a Wikidata project. Beginning with a brief explanation of Wikidata, she outlines four stages of designing a project: Define the objective and scope, Identify data sources, Research and blogging, and Seek opportunities for collaboration.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Syllabus</title>
      <link>//templedss.github.io/LEADING/syllabus/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Jul 2022 14:30:34 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//templedss.github.io/LEADING/syllabus/</guid>
      <description>Curriculum Sample work of art Week 1 Project Overview and Intro to Wikidata Overview of Editing Github
Permissions Documentation Tutorials Introduction to Tracks
Photogrammetry with Polycam and Blender Story Mapping with ArcGIS StoryMaps Unity for Android Wikidata and SPARQL/Python data viz Overview of Editing Wikidata
Week 2 Querying Wikidata with SPARQL and Python Intro to Sparql
Intro to Python with Google Colab Notebooks
Week 3 Working with Github and Github Pages Basics of Git Github Pages Web frameworks Week 4 Developing a Website with Github Deciding on a Web Framework Building the Skeleton Web design principles Week 5 Website Design Documenting wikidata or 3d modeling work Generating content for the website </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Python</title>
      <link>//templedss.github.io/LEADING/post/python/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Apr 2017 11:13:32 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//templedss.github.io/LEADING/post/python/</guid>
      <description>Python allows us to query the Wikidata API easily.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Introducing SPARQL</title>
      <link>//templedss.github.io/LEADING/post/sparql/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Apr 2017 11:00:59 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//templedss.github.io/LEADING/post/sparql/</guid>
      <description>SPARQL is</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Introducing Wikidata</title>
      <link>//templedss.github.io/LEADING/post/wikidata/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Apr 2017 10:58:08 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//templedss.github.io/LEADING/post/wikidata/</guid>
      <description>Summarize querying wikidata</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>//templedss.github.io/LEADING/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//templedss.github.io/LEADING/about/</guid>
      <description>Sample work of art The project team includes:
Synatra Smith, Philadelphia Museum of Art
Alex Wermer-Colan, Temple University
Holly Tomren, Temple University
Pelle Tracey, University of Michigan</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>//templedss.github.io/LEADING/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//templedss.github.io/LEADING/contact/</guid>
      <description>This is an example of a custom shortcode that you can put right into your content. You will need to add a form action to the the shortcode to make it work. Check out Formspree for a simple, free form service.
Your Name Email Address An email address is required. Message </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
